# Camila Paladines

## **Frontend Developer**

(+57) 321 425 7485 · Colombia · camilapaladines.netlify.app · camilapaladines27@gmail.com

I'm a Frontend Developer with 3 years of experience in React and React Native. I have worked with TypeScript, Firebase, HTML, CSS, SCSS and JavaScript. I have built responsive and engaging web interfaces and mobile applications, with a focus on delivering high-quality work that fits user requirements. I have a C1 level of professional English.

## **Experience**

Piyion

June 2022 - Present

Frontend Web / Mobile Developer

- Developed responsive web interfaces using React, TypeScript and Firebase services, creating client interactions based on the provided design specifications.
- Built a mobile application using React Native, TypeScript, SCSS and Firebase services.
- Consumed REST APIs to retrieve and display data within web and mobile applications.

#### Ninus Design & Technology

March 2022 - June 2022

Frontend Web Developer

- Developed responsive web interfaces using React and SCSS, creating client interactions based on provided design specifications.
- Consumed REST APIs to retrieve and display data within the application.
- Debugged and tested all functionality to ensure high quality deliverables that fit user requirements.

## **Projects**

- **Alle Shop** | E-commerce web app | React · TypeScript · TailwindCSS · Firebase
- Calculator App | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- Sunnyside Agency | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- Card Details | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS
- **Space Tourism** | Frontend Mentor challenge | React · TypeScript · SCSS

#### Education

#### Pontificia Universidad Javeriana

Cali, Colombia

Computer Science and Engineering

2018 - 2022

Honors and awards: Honorable Mention to Degree Work, Academic Excellence Scholarship

#### Skills

- Languages: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- Libraries & Frameworks: React, React Native, TailwindCSS
- Tools & Platforms: Git, GitHub, Firebase, Figma, Scrum

### **Social**

- github.com/paladinescamila
- linkedin.com/in/paladinescamila